你那个点子太普通了
Your idea was so simple.
就好像是开会时在屋子里
It was like something you could come up with
现想出来的一样
in the room during a meeting.
周五计算机本科联谊会的时候
Which is what Garrett from Coleman Blair told us
科尔曼布莱尔的盖勒特就这么说的
at the CS undergrad mixer on Friday.
你好  埃利希
Hey, Erlich.
这里呢  06届的
Here I am. Class of '06.
-红衣主教队加油  -红衣主教队加油
- Go Cardinal. - Go Cardinal.
总之  我们创立了新的食物界的沙赞
Anyways, we founded our own Shazam-for-food company,
-他是投资人  -没错
- and he's funding us. - Mm-hmm.
-哇  恭喜啊  -等等  你们这是偷窃
- Whoa, congrats! - Wait, that's stealing.
不是  达头蒂教授给我们看的电影里
No. It's exactly what Mark Zuckerberg did to the Winkle guy
扎克伯格就是这么对付温克莱斯们的
in that Facebook movie Professor Bighetti had us watch.
那部电影里  显然他才是胜者
And he was the hero of that film.